akenai yoru kazoe nagara
While counting the everlasting nights
sugisatta hi omoi tsuzuketa
I kept recalling days past
meguru yume no naka kiete yuku kageboushi
A recurring dream of a fading silhouette
afureru tsui no negai
A cascade of final wishes
tsukiru koto nai koukai no hate
The end of everlasting regret
ka no kishi watarenu mama
Unable to pass into nirvana
orokana hana to chiru
The foolish flower will scatter
tsutsumare ibuku toa no yami
Enveloped by the immortal darkness
tsumetasugite mogaku dake no meguri yo
Frozen by the encroaching night
“Karenaide watashitachi wa utsukushii mama…”
“Unwilted, our beauty will live on…”
odorou yo ikusen no tsuki
Let us dance for thousands of moons
tozasareta me wo eguru you ni
And pry open closed eyes
honoka ni yure, anata izanau
A faint vibration entices you in
“Ochite warau wa, dare…?”
“Who has fallen into laughter…?”